Hello friends, welcome to our
video. In this video, we are going to
see stocks in which
trades can be found for swing trading. So,
our first stock is Angel One.
According to this trend line, support of 2800
is being formed in Angel One. So, here, the
candle which was formed yesterday, like a doji, breaks,
we will make an entry in it and
our stop loss will be 2800 and
our target will be 3600, which is
becoming the resistance of the upward trend line.
And our second stock is ICICI Lombard
General Insurance. Support of 1800 is being formed in this stock.
Here this W
pattern can be formed. So, if
a reversal candle is formed at the level of 1800, then we will
trade in it and our first target will be
000. If there is a breakout after that, then
it will be a breakout of the W pattern
and we will hold it and
then our target in this, its all-time
high level of 2300 will be our target
and our third stock is Kan Board
Biotech.  A breakout of 2200 can be
seen, if a
breakout happens here then we
will make an entry in it and our stop loss in it will be the
low of the breakout candle and its
target which is its all time high of 2600 will be
our target, so friends, in this video
I have told you about three stocks,
which stock did you like, please
tell me in the comment and if you liked the
information given by me then please
like the video and subscribe to our channel.